# **Brittany Plummer**

Rocky Hill CT, 06067 (203) 273-0697 | brittanyplummer@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/brittany-plummer-25manageme https://github.com/BrittPlum

## **Summary of Qualifications**

Exceptional with time management as well as being a proactive listener and communicator. Always punctual and capable of maintaining a professional attitude while still being friendly to customers. Over 5 years of previous customer service experience and gained great team work and communication skills. Recently taken computer programing boot camp cohort online class and learned the fundamentals of website and programming design and logic. Seeking to gain professional experience in information technology and computer programming.

### **Technical Skills**

- Version Control
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- MySql
- MongoDB

- Node.JS
- Coding
- Debugging
- Testing
- Applications
- Modeling
- Responsive Design

- React
- Microsoft Office (Outlook, Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Google Suite
- Slack
- Zoom

### **Education**

Computer Programming Certification | July 2021 | UCONN CODING BOOTCAMP Associates Degree in Science | NORTHWESTERN CONNECTICUT COMMUNITY COLLEGE

# **Relevant Project Experience**

UCONN Coding Boot Camp; Remote

Project One: Lyrichord

- 01/2021 Present
- Led team to create an application that generates lyrics and chords from a specific song search utilizing API calls
- CSS was incorporated using Bulma framework to create well designed and responsive website
- Collaborated cooperatively using the github merge
- Technologies used: HTML5, JavaScript, ¡Query, CSS, Bulma (framework)

#### Project Two: remoteRecruit

- Brainstormed idea to create remoteRecruit, a dynamic full stack application designed to facilitate the connection between freelancers and employers
- Developed front end as well as JavaScript
- Utilized Minisearch to add search functionality to the application
- Communicated clearly to support team and help with task delegation
- Problem solved as team and collaborated to find solutions when application failed functionality tests

### **Experience**

Walmart; Torrington, CT

11/2020 - 02/2021

### **Customer Service Representative**

- Answered telephones and assisted customers find and purchase merchandise
- Checked shipment, scanned for inventory, and placed on sales floor
- Utilized computer system to input paint specifications for mixing
- Operated Point of Sale cash register to check out customers

Private In-Home Care; Goshen, CT & Weatherly, PA

07/2009 - 05/2020

#### **Personal Health Aide**

- Provided overall care to one adult female in Goshen from 2009 to 2019 and one male in Weatherly from 2019 to 2020
- Assisted with hygiene, meal preparation and feeding, handling finances, physical therapy, and transporting to doctor's visits and other errands
- Monitored specific health conditions including setting up Dialysis and Oxygen machines